hello everyone this is Kailash we are
going to use this Python script to web
scrapping here we have new eg website we
are going to collect few basic data for
a graphic card such as its name the
brand the price and also the shipping
price some of them are free and some of
them yeah here for example this 3 point
$99 for shipping ok this is our script
I'm going to run it here ok it's done it
creates a CSV file and you can see the
output here lets me just expand it ok
these are product names after that its
brand name price and the shipping cost
so all of them as I mentioned before is
free and sometimes high price for it ok
this is a web scraping script in Python